D-Did... I'm sorry
did you just say
it's Rachel?
Yes.
Um, you-you
like Rachel?
Yes. I like Rachel.
Rachel?!
Yeah, okay
( stammering )
Hey, you know... you
know who else I like?
You. And-and it doesn't
get said enough.
I like you, Ross.
R-R-Rachel Rachel?
Yeah. It's not a big deal.
It's not a big deal?
Oh, I'm sorry. I just...
Um, I... What about all
the stuff you-you just said?
I mean, how about, uh, like
you can't stop thinking
about her.
Like, how you can't sleep.
I-I'm an actor, you know.
As-As a group we tend
to be overdramatic.
But Rachel-who's-carrying-
my-baby Rachel?
Look, no, I-I know it's bad
and I know it's wrong, okay?
But-But it's not like anything's
ever going to happen, you know.
These-These are just feelings.
They-They're going to go away.
You know, I-I got to go.
Aw, come on, Ross.
Hey, Ross, Ross...
I don't...
I just... you know
I-I just have one...
Rachel?!
( sighs )
( no audio )
Rachel?!
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
Yeah. Oh, oh!
Okay, she's kicking.
Oh.
She's growing inside you.
Whoa! Ooh.
Oh!
Wow, that was a big one.
I think that's
the youngest girl
ever to reject me.
Oh, hey,
you guys.
Oh, hey, there.
Hi.
Hey, listen,
let me ask you.
Do you believe
in soul mates?
Oh, yes, I do.
I do. I believe that there
is one perfect person out there
for everyone.
And you know how you find him?
You stop looking for him.
That's why I've stopped looking
for Russell Crowe.
He'll find me.
Uh-huh, uh-huh.
And you?
No. I mean, I believe that, uh
certain people are more suited
for each other
and I believe in falling in love
but soul mates--
I don't think they exist.
Okay, good.
Why?
Well, last night,
I met Monica's.
( gasps )
What?
Yeah. I-I had a date
with this guy
and I swear to God
he is her other half.
Come on,
don't be crazy.
You don't think
there's somebody out there
better suited for Monica
than me, do you?
Well, what's he like?
Well, he's tall.
Uh-huh.
He has brown hair.
Of course, of course.
A tall guy with hair similar
to mine.
Oh, unknowable universe.
He works with food.
Oh, sure. Older?
Obviously. And he's British.
Oh, I was just
going to ask!
Yeah?
And he's-he's so centered
and mature
and confident.
Oh...
it's so sad they never had
a chance to meet.
Luckily the guy she settled for
can't hear
what you're talking about.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Um, and maybe I'm wrong.
I... but, you know what?
I'm going to go out with him
again and I'll find out more.
You believe that this guy
is destined for somebody else
and you're still going
to date him?
Well, he may not be my soul mate
but a girl's got to eat.
( knocking )
Hey.
I just talked to Joey
and I just...
I wanted to see how you were.
You know what, I still...
I can't believe it.
Joey and Rachel?
I mean it...
It's like you and me going out,
only weirder.
All right, I know you're hurting
and-and I want to be supportive
but don't say that again.
Oh, my God, what if-if they
get married?
Then he'd be the step-father
of my child.
Oh, honey
I don't think that's something
you need to worry about.
First of all, he-he's
never going to tell her
how he feels about her.
And even if he did,
you have no idea
how she would react.
Sure, 'cause women never
like Joey.
You know, I think he's
a virgin.
But Joey...
he's not even thinking about
going after Rachel.
He's not?
No.
All he's thinking about
is how you're taking this.
I mean, listen, it-it's
completely freaking him out.
He's talking about moving
to Vermont.
Why?
He says he wants to leave
the country.
He thinks you hate him.
Hate him? I...
No, I don't hate him.
It's just, it's Rachel,
you know?
Honey, I can't even imagine
how hard this must be for you.
But I don't want you
to lose Joey over it.
Right now he just needs to know
that you're still his friend.
Okay. Okay,
I'll talk to him.
Okay.
And do it soon.
He just asked me
how he could convert his dollars
into Vermont money.
( Phoebe chuckling )
Oh!
Hey.
Oh.
Hi.
Um...
Chandler, Monica,
this is Don.
Hey.
Hello.
Nice to meet you.
( coughs ):
Soul mate.
So, what have
you guys been doing?
Well, we just had
a terrible lunch at Adriatica.
What is with all the sun-dried
tomatoes at that place?
I know. What is this, 1985?
That's exactly what I said.
Phoebe,
isn't that strange?
Not really.
What's wrong with
sun-dried tomatoes?
On a barbecue
chicken pizza?
No?
So, Don,
wh-what other
restaurants do you like?
Well, Octovio,
27 and 7.
Oh, there's this great
little place, Alessandro's.
Oh, my God,
that's my restaurant.
I'm the chef there.
You're kidding me.
No.
Y-Your food is fantastic.
Wow, I really want to talk
to you about your menu.
I'm just going to get
some coffees first.
Um, anyone want anything?
Oh, I'd like a latte.
You know what, if you're going
to talk about me
I'm going to go
with you.
What are you doing?!
Nothing.
I swear to God, I didn't know
you guys would be here.
The good news is, you don't even
believe in soul mates, so...
I believe in tall, handsome
strangers who hit on my wife.
They're just talking.
And you know what, just 'cause
I think they're soul mates
doesn't mean anything's
going to happen.
Phoebe?
Huh?
Good work.
Yeah?
Yeah, I mean, he's great.
I love him.
Don't worry,
we'll find you someone else.
( knocking )
Hey.
Look, I understand
if you came by to hit me.
I deserve it.
No, I-I don't
want to hit you.
Oh, what then? Kick me?
No.
Bite me?
No. No, I don't-I don't
want to do anything to you.
I just want to tell you that
I'm not mad at you, and...
and that I certainly
do not hate you.
I just came here
to say that.
Hey, wait, Ross, Ross.
You want-you want to come in
for a beer or something?
I don't know.
Yeah, sure.
You, uh, you got
any beer?
All-all I got is this,
uh, melon stuff
that Rachel left.
Okay.
Hey, look, Ross, you
need to understand
something, okay.
I, uh...
I am never going to act
on this Rachel thing, okay?
I-I wouldn't want
to do anything
to jeopardize my
friendship with you.
Thank you.
Mmm.
( groans )
Anyway, it, uh...
Look, it-it'll just...
take me a while to get
over her, that's all.
I'm not even sure
how to do that.
I mean, I've never
been in love before
so...
What? You're...?
( sighs )
You're in love with her?
Well, yeah.
I thought you knew that.
Um, no.
Well, hey, look,
if-if it helps
I don't want
to feel this way.
Honest.
I just keep thinking
"Aah, I'll get over
this, you know."
But... God, it just keeps
getting harder, and I...
I don't... I don't know what
to do, you know.
I don't... What do I do?
I think you-you need to
tell her how you feel.
Okay, that's the green stuff
talking.
No, I'm serious.
You... you need to find out
where she is
because if she's not
where you are
then you can start
to move past this.
But what if, uh...
and I'm not saying
she will be...
If-if she is where you are,
then, uh...
then my feeling weird about it
shouldn't stand in the way.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Look, if-if she's going
to end up with somebody else
the truth is, she couldn't find
a better guy, so...
Hey, thanks.
So when do you think
you're going to talk to her?
Oh, my God, I have to tell her.
I haven't even thought about
what I would say.
What should I say?
I'm understanding,
but let's not get carried away.
Right, right.
Sorry, sorry.
( sighs ):
What am I going to say?
Oh!
Yeah, tell me about it.
So, I've been slowly phasing out
the wine importing
and focusing more on
the, um, cheese side of things.
Cheese, you say?
That's some pretty
smelly work, huh, Don?
Excuse me?
Cheese, it's... smelly.
You must smell
a lot of the time, too.
Uh, not really.
But when it comes to cheese,
I'm one of those people
who thinks the smellier,
the better.
Me, too.
Yeah, Chandler can't stand it.
He won't even allow me to have
blue cheese in the house.
And you're still married to him?
( laughing )
( feigns laughter )
You know what
I'd love to do?
Hmm?
I would like
to go to France
and eat nothing
but bread and cheese.
Hmm!
No, not even bread.
Just cheese.
Hmm.
No, I want the
bread, yeah.
And pastries.
Mmm...
And paté.
Oh, I'm really not high.
It's just that
I used to be fat.
Oh! Well, if ever you're in
the Loire Valley, let me know.
I've got a great little villa
you could stay at.
Is it made of cheese?
No.
But God, a house made of cheese!
Wouldn't that be incredible?
I'd move in tomorrow.
Oh, come on!
Are you listening to this?
I'm so sorry.
What do I do?
I don't know.
They both want to live
in a house of cheese.
I don't know how you fight that.
Okay, okay. I can do this.
I can tell her how I feel.
Just, uh...
Okay, stand up straight.
Take a couple deep breaths.
( exhaling )
Look confident.
Oh!
Geez!
Oh, Joey!
Hey.
What's up?
I, uh...
I just came by because I-I want
to talk to you about something.
Okay. What's up?
Here? In the hall?
What are we, animals?
Oh, well, honey,
I'm late for a meeting
so could you just make it quick?
Yeah, okay, um, I just came by
to tell you that...
I... want to have dinner
with you tonight.
That's all.
Sure.
Sounds great.
Just leave me a message
and tell me
where to meet you, okay?
Okay... Great.
Okay.
That's good. Yeah.
Okay, that gives you
a couple of hours
to prepare
what you're going to say.
Good, yeah.
Oh!
Don't you people
ever knock?
I'd like to have
Don and Phoebe over.
Wouldn't that be nice?
Sure.
Why don't you set it up?
I'll just be over here,
browsing through the personals.
Are you okay?
You've been acting
weird all afternoon.
Yeah, fine, fine.
Not perfect!
But good enough.
Geez, what is with you?
I'm sorry.
Did you say "cheese"?
All right,
what's going on?
Phoebe thinks that you
and Don are soul mates.
And I don't believe
in that kind of stuff
but then you two
totally get along.
So look, I won't
stand in your way
if you want to
run off with Don
and live in a
house of cheese.
Chandler, you don't believe
in soul mates?
No, but I'm sure
"to-mah-toes" does.
I don't believe
in soul mates, either.
You don't?
No.
I don't think
that you and I
were destined
to end up together.
I think
that we fell in love
and we work hard
at our relationship.
Some days,
we work really hard.
So, you don't want to live
with Don in a cheese house?
No, I've had second thoughts
about that.
Do you realize how hard
that would be to clean?
I love you.
I know.
You know what?
I'm going to take you
out to dinner tonight.
I found this place
that makes the greatest
mozzarella sticks
and jalapeno poppers.
No? Really?
They taste so good.
I mean, I know
Chandler was kidding
but it happens every time
he touches my stomach.
I mean, I'm really worried
the baby's not
going to like him.
Are you okay?
Well, yeah, sure.
Uh...
Look, the, uh,
the reason...
Is it hot in here?
No, not for me.
But why don't you take off
your sweater?
I would, but this
is a nice place
and my T-shirt
has a picture
of Calvin doing Hobbes.
Oh, my God!
Really?
Can I see it?
Yeah, sure.
Yeah.
Huh!
Wow, I wouldn't think Hobbes
would like that so much.
Uh...
How long have we
known each other?
Um... seven, eight...
eight years.
Wow.
Uh-huh.
Long time.
Yeah.
But over the past
few weeks...
I...
Okay!
( sighs ):
Sorry about the wait
but it is megajammed in here.
We have
a couple specials tonight.
Actually, uh, could
you give us a second?
Sure. Sure.
Second's up.
Not... that kind of table.
( Rachel clears her throat )
So, you were saying?
I'm not quite sure.
Okay, well, you had asked me
how long we knew each other
and I said eight years.
And then the, um,
waiter came over
and cut his tip in half.
And, um, now here we are.
Yeah.
Here we are.
Uh...
I...
I think I'm falling
in love with you.
What?
I'm falling in
love with you.
Who you talking to?
Oh, you're kidding.
Oh, it's a joke.
( silverware clanging )
Oh, that's funny.
It's funny.
I don't get it.
Oh.
Okay.
Um...
Uh, wow.
Are you, um...?
How did, um...?
When?
Does it really matter?
Wow, wow, wow.
Wow, it is hot in here.
Okay, look, look,
Rach, I know this
is a lot, okay?
You don't have
to say anything.
You-you, uh...
You take as much
time as you need.
Okay, you got
to say something.
Joey, Joey...
I love you so much.
But I...
But...
Joey?
Yeah, right.
Hey, that's, um...
That's okay.
That's fine.
That's, um...
pretty much what I was
expecting, you know.
So, uh, it's no
big deal, all right?
I think I'm going to go.
No!
Yeah.
No, Joey, please, don't...
Please don't leave like this.
Now, come on.
( sobbing ):
You cannot do this
to a pregnant woman.
Don't start doing that.
You can't do that, Rach
( sobbing ):
'cause then you're
going to make me do...
And... oh, there we go!
Can I...?
Oh...
Aw, Joey, honey
I don't want...
I don't want to lose...
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
You can't, okay?
Ever.
I'm so sorry.
No, no, no, Rach.
Please, don't be sorry.
Okay?
Don't be sorry.
( sniffles )
( sighs )
( whispers ):
It's all right.
You know what?
I was only kidding.
( giggles )
Yeah, that was a real good one.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
Is this your table?
Yeah.
God, you're going to be here
all night.
I know.
I haven't even read them
the specials yet.
What's the matter with them?
( sighing ):
I don't know.
I think maybe
one of them is dying.
Man...
Hmm, I kind of hope
it's the girl.
The guy is really cute.